hitsniffer.com 2014-06-27

# Real Time Website Tracking Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Hit Sniffer uses and protects any information that you give Hit Sniffer when you use this website.  
Hit Sniffer is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
Hit Sniffer may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from [date].  
**What we collect**   
We may collect the following information:

  *     * name and job title
    * contact information including email address
    * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
    * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

    * Internal record keeping. 
    * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
    * We may periodically send promotional emails **** about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address that you have provided. 
    * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies**   
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.   
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.   
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@hitsniffer.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Hit Sniffer, 16 Worcester Road, Wisbech, PE13 3PB, United Kingdom.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## COOKIE POLICY

Hit Sniffer uses cookies to help us track how you are using the system, diagnose problems and to provide the best browsing experience for you. 

Cookies save you time as they help us to remember who you are. Cookies help us to be more efficient. We can learn about content that is important to you. We can revise or remove web pages that are not of interest and focus our energies on content that you want. 

Here is the list of cookies that hitsniffer uses:

> Hitsniffer Website

PHPSESSID: Default php session handler  
id: holds your account number  
user: holds your username ( nickname )  
email: holds your login email  
pass: holds your password in an encrypted format, then hashed mode ( it is safe )  
nomobile: help to show the desktop version of the website for modern mobile users  
hs_notifysound: identifies if a user choses to play a notification sound when a new visitor visits your own website  
hs_notifymsg: identifies if a user choses to view a notification message when a new visitor visits your own website  
user_country: holds user country value to detect the correct language to be displayed  
mysitegraphdatasource: identifies a users choice on suitable data source for main graph.  
ew-position: position of widgets in dashboard.  
ctype: identifies user choice on suitable type of graph.  
comment_author_#: wordpress keep default action, hold commenter name.  
comment_author_url_#: wordpress keep default action, hold commenter url.  
comment_author_email_#: wordpress keep default action, hold commenter email.

> Tracking Script

blockip: If you are a webmaster and use the cookie method to opt-out of being counted.  
#_uidx: # is dynamic number, used to identify returning visitors.  
#rsuid: # is dynamic, used to improve returning visitors accuracy.  
camp: used if a visitor visits a campaign page.  
campid: used if a visitor visits a campaign page and holds the visitor ID.  
#baseref: # is dynamic for each website, holds base referer data.  
#_juid: # is dynamic for each website, holds javascript numerical unique value

* We also use facebook, twitter and google+ buttons/widgets which add their own cookies  

Get your free trial to test it yourself. Nothing speaks better than system itself!
